

### **ABOUT ME**

As an 3D Artist and Unreal Engine Developer, with more than 7 years of experience in the field, I'm passionate about exploring the latest technologies and working in teams to create impressive projects. My experience as an Unreal Engine developer and my interest in Virtual Production, Development, Modeling, VFX and the IA technologies has allowed me to develop unique skills in the field of 3D.

I'm always looking for new opportunities to expand my knowledge and work with talented teams in the industry.

I'm open to relocate to continue growing my career.

#### SKILLS

JKILLJ	
3d Max	
Blender	
Vray/Corona	
Unreal Engine	
Blueprint	
C++	
Python	
Rizom UV	
Houdini	
Nuke	
Revit	
Autocad	
Photoshop	
English	
Spanish	
Git	
Perforce	
Teamwork	



juan-maldini.com

Porfolio

/Juanmaldini

/juan-augusto-maldini



# MALDINI, Juan Augusto 3D Artist / Unreal Engine Developer

Maniago, Italy juan.maldini@outlook.com +39 3791944958



2008 - 2014

## **EXPERIENCE**

Archelier Studio / 3D Artist 07/2018 - 10/20 From blueprints to the final product, I lead the modeling of buildings, followed by UV mapping, 07/2018 - 10/2018 texturing, and rendering. Subsequently, I oversee the transition to post-production, ensuring a seamless and polished outcome.

Arktura / 3D Artist 07/2020 - 10/20 Responsible for lighting the virtual scenes, texturing 3D models, and decorating environments 07/2020 - 10/2020 with company products such as HVAC elements and panel decorations across various commer-

3DM Digital / 3D Artist 01/2021- 06/2021 As a General 3D Artist, my role involves decorating scenes to ensure environments appear both realistic and visually appealing, essential for architectural visualization in commerce like animations and renderings.

3DUS / 3D Artist - Unreal Engine Developer 07/2021 - 08/202 As a Technical 3D Artist, I specialize in modeling furniture, buildings, and works of art to create 07/2021 - 08/2023 high-quality representations. Additionally, I develop projects in Unreal Engine 5 for real estate

HITO / 3D Artist - Unreal Engine VR Developer 06/2023 - 09/2023 I collaborate in the development of the VR app and team's pipeline. Focused on technical environments and modeling assets to integrate into the virtual experience.

XL Consulting / 3D Construction Visualizer & BIM Consultant 09/2023 – 01/2 I heavily contributed to the app's development and pipeline, particularly in integrating BIM 4D 09/2023 - 01/2024 models. My tasks involved automating data import from Synchro, iTwin, or SketchUp into Unreal Engine, alongside automating scene setup using Python scripts.

Byzantian Interactive, Inc. / 3D Artist & Unreal Engine Generalist 04/2024 - 06/202 3D Artist & Unreal Generalist specialized in procedural 3D modeling using Houdini, with a focus on integrating assets into Unreal Engine for game design purposes. Proficient in landscape and environment creation using Unreal Engine and procedural content generation tools like PCG and Houdini. Collaborating remotely with a talented team via GitHub for seamless collaborative development.

Freelance / 3D Artist Working independently for different organizations as 3D Artist - Unreal Engine Developer for Architectural representations and Game Productions

Dr. Dalmacio Vélez Sársfield
- High School - Bachelor with Orientation in Natural Sciences

### **EDUCATION**

Build Academia  V-ray For 3DS MAX ArchViz N1	2018
<ul> <li>V-ray For 3DS MAX Professional N2         Certification by BuildGroup ChaosGroup &amp; ItooSoftware Authorized Training Centimage Campus</li> <li>Programación C++ para Videojuegos</li> <li>Virtual Production</li> </ul>	ter. 2022
- Coordinación de VFX DVIZ	2022
Virtual Reality Course for Archviz Codeacademy	2022
- Learn C++ Coderhouse - Diseño 3D (Blender)	2023
Udemy  - Unreal Engine desde 0: Crea 3 Juegos con Blueprints y C++ - Unreal Engine 4 Class: Blueprints - Unreal Engine 4 - Creación de materiales desde 0 a AVANZADO - Unreal Engine 5 - Learn to Make a Professional Main Menu - Master Unreal Engine 4 Desarrollo Videojuegos con Blueprints - 3D Studio Max: Espacios arquitectónicos - Houdini - Procedural Japanese Castle in Unreal Engine - Houdini - Procedural House - Houdini - Master Create Stunning fx - Blender 2.9 Iluminación y Render con Cycles de 0 a EXPERTO - Blender 3D - Model and texture a stylised shield! - Blender 2.9 EXPERTO en Modelado 3D desde CERO hasta Avanzado Rebelway	2022 2021 2020 2021 2020 2019 2023 2023 2023 2024 2024 2024
- Houdini - Introduccion to FX	2024

